You blasted human...
You think you can meddle in my plans?
I swore I'd never let Miss Philia go again!
Prince Osvalt...
Sorry I'm late.
But I'm so glad you're safe!
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Presumptuous fool! You haven't beaten me yet!
Asmodeus... We will defeat you here.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 12
"The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé, Now in Another Kingdom"
Silver Judgment!
Blast him! Dark Matter!
Bow before me, inferior humans!
Your Highness!
It's been four hundred years
since I've felt such power!
All because that pathetic
man broke the seal...
Holy Shield!
This power...
It's so much stronger than when
we fought him on the surface!
Asmodeus is fully revived then, isn't he?
Yes.
We can't let him return to the surface now.
Big Sis, you'd better not be thinking about
sacrificing your life to take him out.
I would gladly give my life
to save the entire world.
If I could get Asmodeus to drop
his guard for a single second...
Asmodeus, if you let your
power rage unchecked,
you'll damage your Fianna doll.
You're different.
You're unlike Fianna in every way.
That mercenary attitude of yours
is completely unlike her!
You may be her reincarnation,
but you're nothing like her!
I no longer care what happens to your body.
Catastrophe!
Holy Barrier!
Philia!
No...
Magic's run dry, has it?
You may be the "greatest of all time,"
but this proves you're still merely human.
I can't give up yet.
I made a promise to Prince Osvalt...
At a time like this, my first thought
is about the promise we made?
I see.
You heart lies with the
prince of Parnacorta, then?
Interesting.
I wonder how you'll react when I
tear him to shreds before your eyes!
Don't...
And not just the Parnacortan prince.
I'll have you watch as I beat
everyone you care about to death!
I want to protect them,
the people... I care about...
even if it costs my life.
Philia Adenauer.
I have heard your plea.
You're the saint who saved
the kingdom, Fianna Aesfill.
I must ask your forgiveness.
Because the seal I created was imperfect,
I've made terrible trouble for you.
Philia Adenauer, I now
entrust my power to you.
Wh-What...
Fianna!
That's you, isn't it, Fianna?!
Do you know how long I've waited for this?
Asmodeus, you are simply incorrigible.
I warned you not to cause
any further harm to our world.
Saint Heal!
I'm so glad you're all safe.
Miss Philia?
I will see to Asmodeus.
Leave this to me.
A mere human? Don't make me laugh!
Wait for me, Fianna!
I'll liberate you from that body at once!
He's unleashing that big spell again, Philia!
Silver Judgment!
It won't be enough.
Your pathetic little spells—
I-Impossible. You were
faster at casting than I?
I-It can't be!
Th-That which sealed me away
four hundred years ago...
El Nortia.
You shan't revive so easily again.
I'm going to smash your soul to pieces.
Fianna! Wait!
Please, wait!
All I want is you!
I don't need anything else!
I love you!
I am not Saint Fianna.
Perhaps it was desperation
for love that made you do all this,
but as a saint,
I cannot condone your actions.
Don't do this!
Prepare yourself.
Fianna, I love y—
Thank you for saving the world,
Philia Adenauer.
That is simply the duty of a saint.
Are you all right, Miss Philia?
Yes.
I would be dead had you not
arrived when you did.
Thank you for coming to save me.
Of course I did!
After all, Miss Philia, I... Well, I...
You what?
Time to get going.
You can't say that in this gloomy old hole!
Pick somewhere with
better atmosphere, okay?
I suppose you do have a point.
The mood is important and all.
Where am I?
Philia? What are you doing here?!
It has been some time, Prince Julius.
You cold-hearted woman!
I'm sure it's your fault
that Mia betrayed me, too!
You simply never cease to vex me!
If not for you—
Hey, watch it.
It's fine.
Miss Philia?
Perfect timing, though.
Now I can use my new power to—
Wait, where's my new power?!
Give it up, Girtonian princeling.
Who are you?!
Get your dirty hands off me!
Well, I much prefer to dine on the
disdain of beautiful ladies...
But I wouldn't mind munching on
a snotty little brat for a change.
Wah! Smackity splat.
Mammon, take that loser
to the Girtonian prison.
Yeah, yeah. Give a demon
a break for once, Big Sis.
Let's go back, Miss Philia...
to the others.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
All right.
Philia!
Thank goodness...
I'm so glad you're back!
Mia, I'm sorry I worried you.
No... I'm just glad you're all right.
Prince Osvalt, thank you
for bringing my sister back.
Teacher?
Philia?
I had many chances to tell
you the truth before now.
Forgive me for keeping you
in the dark for so long.
Teacher, please don't bow to me.
Mia told me what happened,
though I'm sure she found
it hard to talk about.
You taught me many things.
To survive, not just as
a saint, but as a person.
You're the reason that I am who I am today.
But I never gave you the
mother's love you deserved...
You did.
More than I could ever expound upon.
My body, my power, my life...
They are all precious to me.
So thank you, Teacher...
No, Mother.
It almost feels inappropriate...
I haven't done a single
motherly thing for you.
There is so much more
I wish to learn from you.
Things I've wondered about since the day
I learned that you were my mother.
I believe you already know the broad strokes.
I don't see how else I can enlighten you.
I want to know about my real father.
Teacher?
That's a natural curiosity, isn't it?
Yet for some reason, I didn't expect it.
Perhaps, knowing you,
I wasn't anticipating ordinary questions.
Is it that strange?
How curious.
She seems so surprised about it...
Your father was a healer.
He had incredible gift for healing wounds.
He died during an epidemic,
but he worried over you until the end.
I see.
Perhaps my talent for healing
magic comes from my father, then.
Sorry...
But is that all?
What do you mean?
Well...
I'm interested to hear where
and how the two of you met,
how you courted, and then eventually
came to be married.
You really are full of questions.
You almost sound like Mia.
You've told Mia all of this?
She doesn't know the meaning of restraint.
Very well.
I'll give you what you want.
I always intended to give
you anything you asked for.
Do you like it, Miss Hildegarde?
Saint Philia informed us
of your penchant for seafood,
What a feast
so I availed myself to its creation.
Leonardo, this is much too much!
No need to worry.
We know how much Saint Philia loves to eat.
Philia? You eat this much?
Since coming to Parnacorta...
Yes, I suppose.
Leonardo's food is just so delicious.
Philia, you've been blessed
with fine companions.
I was worried at first when I heard
you'd been sent to Parnacorta,
but seeing you now makes me realize
that my worries were unfounded.
Yes. I'm grateful to all of them every day.
Miss Philia.
I'm sorry about your parents.
I'm sure you're worried about Miss Mia, too.
So if you'd like...
I'm not going back.
This kingdom no longer needs me.
They have my teacher,
as well as a proper saint.
Big Sis, shouldn't you go give
Philia there a proper goodbye?
Nah.
As long as she remains
the greatest of all time,
I'm sure we'll cross paths again eventually.
People are constantly pestering me
to bring Miss Philia back somehow.
I was wondering if you could convince her.
I have no right to do so.
It would be utterly shameless, really.
That's true.
We have to bring prosperity to our
kingdom ourselves, by hook or by crook.
Responsibility for the foolish decision
to sell Miss Philia to Parnacorta
doesn't fall on Julius alone.
It lies with everyone who didn't stop him.
Prince Fernand...
And I bear the greatest
responsibility of all.
Until you inspired me, fear of my brother
and my own weakness kept me paralyzed.
I won't make excuses.
There's no need to dwell on the past.
You've reflected on what you've
done and begun to move forward,
guiding Girtonia in a better direction.
We're making progress now.
Don't you think it's a shame
to waste time on regret?
You're incredible.
I mean...
You truly are incredible.
Er, shall I take that as a compliment?
Of course, Mia.
The things you say to me give me strength.
I feel like I can do anything.
Your Highness! Saint Mia!
May I have a moment?
If you find value in the things I say,
I will speak with you every day.
Prince Reichardt.
My recent selfish actions were
unbecoming of a saint of Parnacorta.
Please forgive me.
Don't apologize, Philia.
You wished to save your loved ones,
whom you left in your homeland.
I fully understand your feelings...
as well as Osvalt's in aiding you.
I would have done the same
thing for Elizabeth, I'm sure.
Nevertheless, should we find ourselves
in similar circumstances again,
I will still try to stop you.
As saint, you are the key
to our kingdom's prosperity,
which we must protect at all costs.
My kingdom is everything to me.
Philia, please continue
to look after our kingdom.
I will.
Not merely as saint, but as a citizen
of this kingdom I treasure...
I intend to do everything I can.
One Month Later
Big Sister!
It's been so long!
Okay, not really that long,
but are you doing well?!
Yes.
I'm glad to see you healthy as well.
You too, Mother.
I'm still not used to being called that.
The Saint Summit that gathers
all the saints in one place...
Who could serve as its star but I?!
Wh-Who is that?
Well, if it isn't Philia Adenauer!
That would be Emily Mattilas,
saint of Bolmern, yes?
You were so invisible I barely noticed you!
I've never met her before, but...
Come, Amanda, Jane!
Of the current saints, she is likely
the closest to you in terms of power.
Except her personality
is the polar opposite...
Saint Philia!
It's been ages!
They're going to let me stay
and keep studying under you!
I can't wait to spend lots
more time with you!
Good. You work very hard,
so I enjoy teaching you.
What a nice thing to say!
Hey, hang on!
Stop clinging to her like a little sister!
She's my big sis!
Mia.
As it happens, I'm Saint Philia's
number one student!
There's absolutely nothing wrong
with me treating her like an elder sister!
Sister! Who is this girl?!
Oh, that's right!
As thanks for the hairpin you
gave me, I got you a present.
It looks perfect on you, Saint Philia!
It seems a bit extravagant...
Miss Mia's taste is as excellent as ever.
I'm sure Prince Osvalt will be so busy
staring, he won't be able to eat!
Please, don't tease me...
You don't think he'll laugh at me?
He would never do that!
I'm certain he'll compliment your look.
D-Do you think so?
You're so young, Saint Philia.
I just hope you enjoy yourself.
Leonardo, this is no laughing matter.
Do pardon me.
It's simply so rare to see you act in
a manner befitting your age, I was relieved.
I always take the long view, after all.
A manner befitting my age, you say?
Your Highness?
You look splendid.
I mean, you always look lovely...
But I couldn't help staring.
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean you're just beautiful!
Miss Philia.
Do you remember?
When you first arrived in Parnacorta,
I made you a promise...
That I'd work hard to make sure
you came to love our country.
Yes, I remember.
And since then, I've made
so, so many memories.
I've come to know so many people.
And so I do love this country now.
As saint of Parnacorta,
I hope to continue protecting it.
I'm glad.
I love this country and
the people who live here.
And you, Philia Adenauer...
I love you, too.
S-Sorry! I didn't mean to...
I guess that was too sudden, wasn't it?
No.
Prince Osvalt... It isn't that.
I think I may be crying from happiness.
At least, I believe...
I read in a book that happiness
can stimulate the tear ducts,
causing tears to flow.
I've never seen anyone analyze
their own tears of joy like that before.
But that's just who you are.
I love that about you, too.
Y-You love the ways in which I'm strange?
Well, I think that's what
falling in love is about.
I see.
I understand clearly now, then.
To love someone is truly a
wonderful feeling, isn't it?
And so, the too-perfect saint,
tossed aside by her fiancé
was now in another kingdom,
where she found happiness.